E. P. Dutton & Company, Inc. Records
E. P. Dutton & Company, Inc. Records
- Publicity files
  - Douglas-Home - Druon (Box 63)
    Douglas-Home, Robin
    Drewry, Caleton
    Druon, Maurice
  - Dudintsev - Dupeyrat (Box 63)
    Dudintsev, Vladimir (letters)
    Duncan, Robert
    Dupeyrat, Andre
  - E (misc.) - Egleson (Box 63)
    E (misc.)
    Earl, Lawrence
    Ebby, Lois and Fleming, John
    Egleson, James and Janet
  - Ellenwood - Ellis (Box 63)
    Ellenwood, James Lee
    Ellis, Amanda M.
  - Erickson (Box 63)
    Erickson, Gladys
  - Ernenwein - Evans (Box 63)
    Ernenwein, Leslie
    Evans, Charles
  - Everest - Falkner (Box 63)
    Everest, Lt. Col. Frank K., Jr.
    Falkner, Leonard
  - Felix - Flammarion Dictionary (Box 63)
    Felix, Christopher
    Fere, Natala de la
    Fishbein, Morris and DeLee, Sol Theron
    Flammarion Dictionary
  - Foldes - Ford (Box 63)
    Flenley, Ralph
    Foldes, Andor and Lili
    Ford, Ira W.
  - Fortune - Fuller (Box 63)
    Fortune
    Fredericks, Pierce G.
    Freedman, Ralph
    Fryer, Katherine Homer
    Fuller, Muriel
  - GA - GM (Box 64)
  - GN - GZ (Box 64)
  - Gambrell - Garland (Box 64)
    Gambrell, Herbert and Virginia
  - Gaskell - Gault (Box 64)
    Gaskell, Jane
    Gatty, Harold
    Gault, William Campbell
  - Gee - Geer (Box 64)
    Gee, E.P.
    Geer, Lt. Col. Andrew
  - Geographies - Geographies, Dutton Advanced (Box 64)
    Geographies
    Geographies, Dutton Advanced
  - Geographies (Box 64)
    Advanced Geographies
  - Ghiselin - Giaever (Box 64)
    Ghiselin, Brewster
    Giaever, John
  - Gibbings, Robert (Box 64)
  - Gifford - Goddard (Box 64)
    Gifford, Captain, Tom
    Glaser, Hugo
    Glasier, Phillip
    Goddard, Dwight
  - Gompers - Goddin (Box 64)
    Gompers, Samuel
    Goodheart, Robert Stanley
    Goodman, Paul
    Goodin, Peggy
  - Goullart - Govinda (Box 64)
    Goullart, Peter
    Govan, Gilbert & Livingood, James W.
    Govinda, Lama Anagarika
  - Grattidge - Gregory (Box 64)
    Grattidge, Capt. Harry
    Gregory, Alyse
  - Grininoff - Groussard (Box 64)
    Grininoff, Vladimir B. (Boris)
    Griswold, George
    Groussard, Serge
  - Gruver - Guiterman (Box 65)
    Gruver, Harold B.
    Guderian, Heinz
    Grzimek, Dr. Bernard and Michael
    Guiterman, Arthur
  - Guppy - Gutman (Box 65)
    Guppy, Nicholas
    Gutman, Walter K.
  - H (misc.) (Box 65)
  - Haas - Hamilton (Box 65)
    Haas, Carola
    Haas, Rosamond
    Hackett, Alice
    Hale, Garth (A.B. Cunningham)
  - Hasen, Henny Harald (Box 65)
  - Hardy - Hart & Lejeune (Box 65)
    Hardy, Jane
    Harlow, Alvin F.
    Harrer, Heinrich
    Hart & Lejeune
  - Hartmann - Heinkel (Box 65)
    Hartman, John
    Harvey, Jack
    Hastings, Phyllis
    Hauge, Eiliv and Hartman, Vera
    Heinkel, Ernst
  - Henrey, Mrs. Robert (Box 65)
  - Henriques - Herzog (Box 65)
    Henriques, Veronica
    Henry, B.A.
    Herzog, Maurice
  - Hewes - Hlasko (Box 65)
    Hewes, Thomas
    Hillary, Sir Edmund
    Hlasko, Marek
  - Hoff - Holt (Box 65)
    Hoff, Syd
    Hokinson, Helen E.
    Holt, Felix
  - Horgan - Howard (Box 65)
    Horgan, Paul
    Horowitz, I.A. and Reinfield, Fred
    Howard, Frances Minturn
  - Hidnut - Hunt (Box 66)
    Hudnut, Elisabeth Ann
    Hunt, Sir John
  - Hunt - Hyman (Box 66)
    Hunter, Robins
    Hyman, Dick
  - Isaacs - Izzard (Box 66)
    Issacs, J.
    Issacs, Julius
    Izzard, Ralph
  - J (misc.) - Johnston (Box 66)
    J (misc.)
    Jaeger, Paul
    Jelagin, Juri
    Johnston, Eric
  - Jones, D. - Jones, S. (Box 66)
    Jones, Sir Harold Spencer
    Jones, Stacey V.
  - Josephs, Ray I (Box 66)
  - Josephs, Ray II (Box 66)
  - K (misc.) - Kehow (Box 66)
    K (misc.)
    Karolyi, Michael
    Keeler, Harry Stephen
    Kehow, William
  - Kellems - Kevenson (Box 66)
    Kellems, Vivien
    Kellino, Pamela
    Keveson, Peter
  - Khruschev - Kish (Box 66)
    Khruschev, Nikita S.
    Kiely, Benedict
    Kirkell & Schaffnit
  - Knight - Koch (Box 66)
    Knight, Clifford
    Koch, Adrienne
  - Kogan, Herman and Wendt, Lloyd (Box 66)
  - Komroff - Kugelmass (Box 66)
    Komroff, Manuel
    Kovach, Nora and Rabovsky, Istvan
    Kreymborg, Alfred
    Kugelmass, I. Newton, M.D.
  - LA to LN (misc.) - Lader (Box 66)
    LA to LN (misc.)
    LN to LZ (misc.)
    Lader, Lawrence
  - Laing - Lane (Box 66)
    Laing, Alexander
    Lamont, Nedda Barnitt
    Lane, Bess B.
  - Langer - Leary (Box 67)
    Langer, Lawrence
    Lawrence, T.E.
    Leary, Francis
  - Lederman - LeToumelin (Box 67)
    Lederman, Martin
    Leeming, John F.
    Lehman, Paul Evan
    Leighton, Alexander H.
    Le Toumelin, Jaques Ives
  - Leyson - Lieberman (Box 67)
    Leyson, Burr W. amd Manecke, Ruth
    Leyson, Capt. Burr W.
    Lieberman, Dr. Elias
  - Life, Editors (Box 67)
  - Life - Lodge (Box 67)
    Life - Worlds Great Religions
    Lightwood, Teresa
    Lockwood, Charles A.
    Lodge, Tom
  - Look - McCormick (Box 67)
    Look: The Story of the FBI
    Lord, David
    Lorris and Meun
    Love, Mabel
    Lucas - Dubreton, J.
    MC & MAC (misc.)
    McCormac, Charles E.
  - McCuaig - McGaughey (Box 67)
    McCuaig, Elizabeth Bonnell
    M'Cutcheon, Hugh
    McGaughey, William H.
  - McGurn - McKinney (Box 67)
    McGurn, Barrett
    McIlwaine, Shields
    McKinney, Howard D. and Anderson, W.R.
  - McKinney - McMullen (Box 67)
    McLean, Maragaret Predergast
    McMullen, Margery
  - Mackworth - Mannerheim (Box 67)
    Mackworth, Cecily
    Magener, Rolf
    Major, Mason, Wright
    Mankowitz, wolf
    Mannerheim, Baron Carl Gustaf
  - Manners - Marion (Box 67)
    Manners, William
    Manser, Ruth B and Mulgrave, Dorothy I.
    Manzoni, Allessandro
    Marchal, Lucien
    Maresca, James V.
    Marion, Frederick
  - Marotta - Marshak (Box 67)
    Marotta, Guiseppe
    Marsh, Corinna
    Marshak, Samuel
  - Martienssen - Mathews (Box 67)
    Martienssen, Anthony K.
    Mason, Kenneth
    Martin, Troy Kennedy
    Mary Francis Louise, Sister
    Mathews, Paul Wentworth
  - Meany - Meoni (Box 67)
    Meany, Tom
    Meckel, Aaron N.
    Meehan, Francis
  - Meredith - Meyrell (Box 68)
    Meredith, Roy
    Meredith, Scott
    Meyer, Jerome S.
    Meynell, Viola
  - Micocci - Molnar (Box 68)
    Micocci, Harriet Palmer
    Migot, Andre M.
    Miller, Max
    Molnar, George
  - Montgomery - Moskowitz (Box 68)
    Montgomery of Almein El Alme in to the River Sangro
    Moorad, George Lost Peace in China
    Morgan, Murray
    Morrel, Martha McBride Young Hickory
    Morris, Katherine
    Moskowitz and Collier Patterns and Ceremonials of the Indians of the Southwest
  - Mukerji - Murray (Box 68)
    Munthe, Dr. Axel
    Murray, Venetia
    Murray, W.H.
  - Myers, J. - Myers, L. (Box 68)
    Myers, Lou
  - N (misc.) - Newell (Box 68)
    N (misc.)
    Nelson, Edna Deu Pree
    Nelson, William and Vandiver, Frank
    Newell, Gordon
  - Nicholl - O (misc.) (Box 68)
    Nureyev
    O (misc.)
  - O'Brian - Owens (Box 68)
    O'Brien, Brian
    O'Mara, Jim
    Opie, June
    Osusky, Stefan
    Owens, Lorena
  - P (misc.) - Papem (Box 68)
    P (misc.)
    Padellaro, Nazareno
    Palmer, J. Arthur
    Papen, Franz von
  - Papini - Phillips (Box 68)
    Papini, Giovanni
    Partridge, Eric
    Perowne, Stewart Henry
    Pettersson, Hans
    Phillips, Alexandria
  - Philpot - Pratz (Box 68)
    Philpot, Oliver
    Pichon, Charles
    Pirenne, Jaques
    Popkin, Zelda
    Pratz, Claire and Lingafelt, Georgia
  - Prechtl - Ralph (Box 69)
    Prechtl, Robert
    Pretorius, Major P.J.
    Prewett, Virginia
    Queffelec, Hanri
    Ralph, Philip Lee
  - Ramsey - Rawson (Box 69)
    Ramsey, Robert
    Rawson, Marion N.
  - Rees - Robertson (Box 69)
    Rees, Gilbert
    Reeves, George S.
    Richter, Christiane
    Roberts, Marion
    Robertson, Frank C.
  - Robertson - Romanis (Box 69)
    Robertson, Terrance
    Robinson, Ione
    Rogers, John William
    Romanis, Robert
  - Rosenberger - Ross (Box 69)
    Rosenberger, Francis Coleman
    Ross, George E.
    Ross, James Davidson
  - Ross - Rutledge (Box 69)
    Ross, James Kenneth Matthews
    Ruth, Babe
    Rutledge, Nancy
  - S (misc.) - Sakai (Box 69)
    S (misc.)
    Sagendorph, Kent
    Saint Pierre, Michel de
    Sakai, Saburo
  - Sanders - Saunders (Box 69)
    Sanders, Allegra
    Sargeant, Winthrop
    Saturday Evening Post
    Saund, D.S.
    Saunders, Edith
  - Savoy - Scarlett (Box 69)
    Savoy, Williard - Alien Land
    Scarbrough, George
    Scarlett, William (Phillips Brooks)
  - Schachtel - Schiaparelli (Box 69)
    Schachtel, Hyman Judah
    Schiaparelli, Elsa
  - Scholes - Scott (Box 69)
    Scholes, Arthur W.
    Schroter, Heinz
    Scott, J.M.
    Scott-James, Anne
  - Scott - Semeonoff (Box 69)
    Scott, Natalie, Anderson
    Scott, Paul
    Seabury, Samuel
    Sellar and Yeatman
    Semeonoff, Anne H.
  - Sforza - Shaw (Box 70)
    Sforza, Count Carlo
    Shakespeare
    Shattock, Rear Admiral Ernest H.
    Shaw, Carolyn Hagner
  - Shepard - Shigemitsu (Box 70)
    Shepard, Odell
    Sherman, Admiral Frederick C.
    Sherman, Ray W.
    Shigemitsu, Mamoru
  - Shipton - Sine (Box 70)
    Shipton, Eric
    Shoemaker, Dr. Samuel M.
    Shore, Wilma
    Shotwell, James T.
    Sine
  - Skolsky - Smith (Box 70)
    Skolsky, Syd
    Skinner, Rosemary
    Smith, Emma
    Smith, Julia
  - Snell - Spingarn (Box 70)
    Solinas, Franco
    Sorokin, Pitirm A.
    Spingarn, Lawrence P.
  - Sproul - Spry (Box 70)
    Sproul, Kathleen
    Spry, Constance and Hume, Rosemary
  - Standen - Starkie (Box 70)
    Standen, Anthony
    Stanford, Doreen
    Starkie, Walter
  - Sterling - Steward (Box 70)
    Sterling, Stewart
    Stevens, William Oliver
    Stevenson, Candance Thurber
    Stewart, Davenport
  - Storm, John (Box 70)
  - Strenkowski - Strong (Box 70)
    Strenkowski, Serge
  - Suba - Surmelian (Box 70)
    Suba, Susanne
    Surmelian, Leon Z.
  - Sutphin - Teale (Box 70)
    Sutphin, Wyn Blair
    Syverson, Henry
    Tallant, Robert
    Teale, Edwin Way
  - Tebbel - Terhune (Box 71)
    Tebbel, John
    Terhune, Albert Payson
  - Terrot - Thomas (Box 71)
    Terrot, Charles
    Thomas, Jean
  - Thomsen - Thompson (Box 71)
    Thomsen, Dr. Alexander
    Thompson, Craig
    Thompson, Nellie Zetta
  - Tiira - Townend (Box 71)
    Tiira, Ensio
    Time Reader's Book of Recipes
    Tisne
    Todd, James and Janet Maclean
    Towend, Paul
  - Traver - Tregaski (Box 71)
    Traver, Robert
    Travis, William
    Tregaskis, Richard
  - Troy - Trussell (Box 71)
    Troy, Una.
    Trumbull, Robert
    Truscott, Lt. Gen. L.K, Jr.
    Trusell, Tait and Hencke, Paul
  - Tsanoff - V (misc.) (Box 71)
    Tsanoff, Rado Slav A
    Tucci, Giuseppe
    Turner, E.S.
    Tyrrell, G.N.M.
    Ulich, Robert
    Underhill, Evelyn
    United Nations
    V (misc.)
  - Vaculik - Van Saher (Box 71)
    Vaculik, Serge
    Van Saher, Lilla
  - W (misc.) - Wagner (Box 71)
    W (misc.)
    Waddell, E.Lee
    Wagenknecht, Edward
    Wagner, Charles
  - Walker - Ward (Box 71)
    Walker, Turnley
    Ward, Brad
  - Wayne - Weigel (Box 71)
    Wayne, Joseph
    Webb, Mary
    Webber, Everett and Olga
    Weigel, Henrietta
  - Welshimer - Westwood (Box 71)
    Welshimer and O'Neill
    West, Ray B., Jr.
    Westerfield, Hargis
    Westley, William
    Westwood, Gordon
  - Wetherell - Wheeler (Box 72)
    Wetherell, June
    Wheeler, John
  - Wheeler - White (Box 72)
  - White - Williams (Box 72)
    Whittaker, James C.
    Williams, Eunice Pollard
    Williams, Prof. Frayne 1934-1940
  - Williams - Willoughby (Box 72)
    Williams, Rebecca Yancey
    Williams, Roy
    Williams, Henry
    Willoughby, Maj. Gen. Charles A.
  - Wilson - Winsten (Box 72)
    Wilson, Jock
    Wilson, Sandy
    Winsten, Stephen
  - Wittmer - Wood (Box 72)
    Wittmer, Margaret
    Womersley, Wilfred
    Wood, Alice L. - Sound Games
  - Wood, A. - Wood, W. (Box 72)
    Wood, Alice
    Wood, Ernest - Practical Yoga
    Wood, Wendy
  - Woodbury - Woodward (Box 72)
    Woodbury, David O. - Builders For Battles
    Woodman, George
  - Wyllie - Wynner (Box 72)
    Wyllie, John
    Wynner and Llyod: Searchlights on Peace Plans
  - Yank - Yoseloff (Box 72)
    The Best of Yank
    Yates, Margaret and Brainlette, Paula - Death Casts a Vote
    Yeats, J.B.
    Yoseloff, Martin
  - Zamperini - Zamiatin (Box 72)
    Zamperini, Louis
    Zamiatin, Eugene
  - Zilles - Zoff (Box 72)
    Zilles, Luke
    Zoff, Otto
- Foreign correspondence
  - Aa - [George] Allen and Unwin (publisher) (Box 73)
  - Am - Az, 1958-1965 (Box 73)
  - Baa - Baz (Box 73)
  - Be - Bl (Box 73)
  - Bo - By (Box 73)
  - Ca - Ce (Box 73)
  - [Jonathan] Cape - Cl (Box 73)
  - Coa - Com (Box 73)
  - Con - Da (Box 73)
  - De - Dj (Box 73)
  - Dent (London) (Box 73)
  - Dent (Canada) (Box 74)
  - Do - Ez (Box 74)
  - Faber & Faber (publisher) - Fo (Box 74)
  - Fr - Ge (Box 74)
  - Gi - Gy (Box 74)
  - Ha - Haz (Box 74)
  - He - Hi (Box 74)
  - Ho (Box 74)
  - Hu - I (Box 74)
  - J (Box 74)
  - Ka - Le (Box 74)
  - Li - Ly (Box 74)
  - Maa - Maz (Box 75)
  - Mc - Me, includes Maurice Michael (Box 75)
  - Methuen - Mo (Box 75)
  - Mu - Ny, includes John Murray (Box 75)
  - O (Box 75)
  - Pa - Q (Box 75)
  - Rainbird - Ry, includes Rainbird (publisher) material on D.B. Wyndham Lewis' The World of Goya (Box 75)
  - Routledge - Sh (Box 75)
  - Si - Sti (Box 75)
  - Sto - Th (Box 75)
  - Ti - Wa (Box 75)
- Children's editor's files
  - Authors - Correspondence, 1950's (Box 76)
  - Ackerman - Bank (Box 76)
    Eugene Ackerman
    Ralph Andrews
    Margot Austin
    Bank Street Project
  - Brown - Caffrey (Box 76)
    Brown, Ann Llama Bean (declined)
    Bluemle Saturday Science (photographs)
    Brown, Ann Towson How Does A Garden Grow?
    Burns, William Exploring For Trees (declined)
    Burns, William Exploring For Fun
    Caffrey, Nancy Hanover's Wishing Star
    Caffrey, Nancy Horse Haven
  - Caffrey - Campbell (Box 76)
    Caffrey, Nancy Pony Duet
    Caffrey, Nancy Scene From The Saddle
    Caidin, Martin By Apollo To The Moon
    Caidin, Martin Aviation and Space Medicine
    Campbell, Marion The Wide Blue Road
    Campbell, Wanda The Museum Mystery
    Campbell, Wanda J. Mystery of Old Mobeetie
    Campbell, Wanda J. Ten Cousins
  - Campbell - Chute (Box 76)
    Campbell, Wanda J. Mystery of McClellan Creek
    Carmer, Carl Pets at the White House
    Chute, Joy
    Chute, Marchette Around and About
    Chute, Marchette Jesus of Israel
    Chute, Marchette The Wonderful Winter
  - Children's - Dahl (Box 76)
    C.I.C.:
    Rupert of Henziau
    The Heroes
    Dickens
    Little Lord Fauntleroy
    The Little Duke
    Odysseus
    Cook, Marion Belden Terry's Ferry
    Cornwall, I.W. and Maitland Howard The Making of Man
    Dahl, Borghild The Daughter
    Dahl, Borghild Karen
    Dahl, Borghild A Minnetonka Summer
  - Dahl - Engle (Box 76)
    Dahl, Borghild Stowaway to America
    Dahl, Borghild Under The Roof
    Delaune, Jewel Lynn Giraffe's Can Be a Trouble
    Derleth, August The Wind Leans West (declined)
    Diekmann, Miep The Haunted Island
    Dillard Maud Esther Ahoy, Peggy Stuart!
    Downey, Glanville Belisarius
    Engle, Paul Golden Child
  - F (misc.) - Fry (Box 76)
    F miscellaneous Authors
    Fairy Tales of Many Lands
    Forsyth, Gloria Pelican Prill
    Freeman, Michael 1962
    Fry, Rosalie A Bell For Ringleblume
    Fry, Rosalie The Echo Song
  - Fry, Rosalie (Box 76)
    The Mountain Door
    Fry, Rosalie Fly Home Columbia
    Fry, Rosalie Secret of the Ron Moor Skerry
    Fry, Rosalie Mateloi, Little Sailor of Brittany
  - Fry - Gault (Box 76)
    Fry, Rosalie The Riddle of the Figurehead
    Fry, Rosalie The Wind Call
    Fuchs, Sir Vivian Antarctic Adventure
    Gault, William Campbell Dirt Track Summer
    Gault, William Campbell Drag Strip
    Gault, William Campbell Rough Road to Glory
    Gault, William Campbell Speedway Challenge
  - Gault (Box 76)
    Gault, William Campbell Little Big Foot
    Gault, William Campbell Wheels of Fortune
    Gault, William Campbell Through the Line
    Gault, William Campbell Dim Thunder
    Gault, William Campbell Mr. Quarterback
    Gault, William Campbell Two-Wheeled Thunder
    Gault, William Campbell Road-Race Rookie
  - George - Grant (Box 76)
    George, Jean My Side of the Mountain
    George, Jean The Hole in the Tree
    George, Jean Snow Tracks
    George, John & Jean The Dipper of Copper Creek
    Glass, Alexander Books on Computer
    Goodin, Peggy Edna St. Vincent Millay book (declined)
    Granberg, W.J. Spread the Truth
    Granberg, W.J. Voyage Into Darkness
    Grant, Bruce & Lorence Bjorklund Pirogue
  - Hall-Quest - Harper (Box 76)
    Hall-Quest, Olga Jamestown Adventure
    Hall-Quest, Olga With Stanley in Africa
    Harper, Wilhelmina Easter Chimes revised edition
  - Hughes - Knight (Box 77)
    Hughes, Toni Toni Hughes' Book of Party Favors & Decorations
    Hutchinson, Paula Dugan of Gravely Dumps
    Hutchinson, Paula Mike the Morning Man
    Johnson, Grace and Harold
    Jupo, Frank J.
    Key, Ted
    King, Robin The Biggest Hat In The World
    King, Robin Burrito
    King, Robin Hundl is a Dog
    King, Robin The Wondrous Egg of Abou
    Knight Alexander's Christmas Eve
  - Lambert (Box 77)
    Lambert, Janet Big Deal
    Lambert, Janet Boy Wanted
    Lambert, Janet Five's A Crowd
    Lambert, Janet Fly Away, Cinda
    Lambert, Janet For Each Other
    Lambert, Janet Forever and Ever
    Lambert, Janet Introducing Parri
    Lambert, Janet Love Taps Gently
    Lambert, Janet Myself and I
    Lambert, Janet Old Titles
    Lambert, Janet The Precious Days
    Lambert, Janet Spring Fever
  - Lambert - Lamorisse (Box 77)
    Lambert, Janet The Stars Hang High
    Lambert, Janet Summer Madness
    Lambert, Janet Wedding Bells
    Lambert, Janet We're Going Steady
    Lamond, Henry G. Towser
    Lamorisse, Albert The Red Balloon (dropped)
    Lamorisse, A., de Daunant White Mane D. Colomb
  - Langdale - McFarland (Box 77)
    Langdale, Hazel The Cocker Spaniel
    LIFE International Editors Nine Who Chose America
    Lyons Sarnoff Story
    McFarland and Sports Midget Motoring
  - McGriffin (Box 77)
    McGriffin, Lee High Whistle Charley
    McGriffin, Lee The Horse Hunters
    McGriffin, Lee Rebel Rider
    McGriffin, Lee Ride for Texas
    McGriffin, Lee Swords, Stars, and Bars
  - McGuire - Massnick (Box 77)
    McGuire, Frances The Case of the Smuggled Ruby
    McSwigan, Marie Small Miracle at Lourdes
    McSwigan, Marie All Aboard For Freedom
    Manning-Sanders A Book of Giants
    Marsh, Corrina Flippy's Flashlight
    Massnick, Forler (Book on Dyna Soar)
  - Mayne - Mellin (Box 77)
    Mayne, William The Glass Ball
    Mayne, William Underground Alley
    Mayne, William A Grass Rope
    Mayne, William The Changeling
    Meigs, Elizabeth Blue Palomino
    Meigs, Elizabeth General
    Mellin, Jeanne Horses Across America
    Mellin, Jeanne Horses Across the Ages
  - Mellin - Milne (Box 77)
    Mellin, Jeanne Pidgy's Surprise
    Milgram, Harry Explorations in Science
    Milne, A.A. Le Meilleur des Ours translated by P. Martin
    Milne, A.A. Pooh Birthday Book
    Milne, A.A. Pooh Coloring Book
    Milne, A.A. Pooh: His Art Gallery
    Milne, A.A. Pooh in I/T/A/
  - Milne - Mudro (Box 77)
    Milne, A.A. Pooh Songbook
    Milne, A.A. The World of Christopher Robin
    Milne, A.A. The World of Pooh
    Mitchell, Elyne The Silver Brumby
    Mitchell, Elyne Snow Filly
    Mitchell, Elyne General
    Mudro, Marie A Feather for His Cap
    Mudro, Marie Look Beyond Tomorrow
  - Nichols - Oberjohann (Box 77)
    Nichols, Beverly The Mountains of Magin (declined)
    Miles, Katherine The Angel in the Hayloft
    North, Sterling Poe the Crow (tent. title) (dropped)
    Oberjohann, Heinrich My Best Friends Are Apes
  - O'Brien - Olgin (Box 77)
    O'Brien, Brian Ivory, Apes and Jimibel
    O'Brien, Brian Scrimshaw and Sudden Death
    O'Brien, Brian Windship Boy
    Olain, Joseph
  - Olgin - Peterson (Box 78)
    Olgin, Joseph Backcourt Rivals
    Olgin, Joseph Little League Champions
    Pordee & Young Lucky Days
    Peterson, Kai and George Zoppler Prehistoric Life on Earth 1957-1958, etc., 1959
  - Peterson - Power-Waters (Box 78)
    Peterson, Kai and George Zoppler Prehistoric Life on Earth 1960
    Peterson, Kai and George Zoppler Prehistoric Life on Earth 1961-1963
    Power-Waters, Alma The Melody Makers
    Power-Waters, Alma Moon In My Pocket
  - Power-Waters - Price (Box 78)
    Power-Waters, Alma Young Edwin Booth
    Power-Waters, Alma Virginia Giant
    Price, Christine Made in the Renaissance
    Price, Christine Made in the Middle Ages
  - Price - Reeves (Box 78)
    Price, Christine The Story of Muslim Art Fall 1964
    Price, Hilda
    Reeves, James The Peddler's Dream
    Reeves, James Ragged Robins
  - Reeves - Ritchie (Box 78)
    Reeves, James Sailor Rumbelow and Other Stories
    Riev, E.V. The Flattered Flying Fish
    Ritchie, Rita The Enemy at the Gate
    Ritchie, Rita The Golden Hawks of Genghis Khan
    Ritchie, Rita The Secret Beyond the Mountains
    Ritchie, Rita The Year of the Horse
  - Robinson - Ruck-Panquet (Box 78)
    Robinson Plutarch
    Ross, George Know Your World
    Ruck-Panquet, Gina Joschko
  - Tefft - Savitt (Box 78)
    Tefft, Bess Merrie Maple
    Terhune, Albert Payson Lad: A Good Dog Anniversary Edition
    Thelwell A Leg at Each Corner
    Todd, Bernice Me Too! (declined)
    St. Johns and Tworkov My Friend God
    Sanger, Marjory B. Greenwood Summer
    Savitt, Sam Midnight: Champion Bucking Horse
    Savitt, Sam Step-A-Bit
  - Schealer, John (Box 78)
    Schealer, John The Sycamore Warrior
    Schealer, John This Way to the Stars
    Schealer, John Zip-Zip Goes to Venus
    Schealer, John Zip-Zip and his Flying Saucer
  - Schealer - Simon (Box 78)
    Schealer, John Zip-Zip and the Red Planet
    Severn, David Clouds Over the Alberhorn (tent.) (dropped)
    Severn, David The Wild Valley Pub. 8/1/63
    Simon, Charlie May All Men Are Brothers
    Simon, Charlie May A Seed Shall Serve
  - Simon - Smith (Box 78)
    Simon, Charlie May The Sun and the Birch
    Smith, Geraldine Foster Little Dog Sniff and the Twins
    Smith, Peery The Hidden Place
    Smith, William Jay Typewriter Town
    Smith, William Jay General
  - Smythe - Sutcliff (Box 78)
    Smythe, Pat Jump For Joy
    Spyri, Johanna All Alone in the World
    Spyri, Johanna The Pet Lambs
    Strachan, Niona Christopher Jarrett of New Plymouth
    Stuart, Dorothy Margaret London Through the Ages
    Sutcliff, Rosemary Beowulf
    Sutcliff, Rosemary The Hound of Ulster Pub. 2\29\64
  - Valens - Vance (Box 78)
    Valens and Seakorg The Elements of the Universe
    Valens and Seakorg Viruses and the Nature of Life
    Valens, Evans Wingfin and Topple (declined)
    Vance, Marguerite Ashes of Empire
    Vance, Marguerite The Boy on the Road
    Vance, Marguerite The Empress Josephine
    Vance, Marguerite Dark Eminence
    Vance, Marguerite Flight of the Wilding: Elizabeth of Austria
  - Vance, Marguerite (Box 78)
    Vance, Marguerite A Flower From Dinah
    Vance, Marguerite Leave it to Linda
    Vance, Marguerite Jeptha and the New People
    Vance, Marguerite The Lamplighters
    Vance, Marguerite Mary Stuart
  - Vance - Watts (Box 79)
    Vance, Marguerite Secret for a Star
    Vance, Marguerite Song for a Lute
    Vance, Marguerite A Star for Hansi
    Vance, Marguerite Willie Joe and His Small Change
    Vance, Marguerite Windows for Rosemary
    Vance, Marguerite The World For Jason Pub. 1961
    Watts, Mabel General
  - Wehen - Wheeler (Box 79)
    Wehen, Joy DeWeese Stairway to a Secret
    Wehen, Joy DeWeese The Tower in the Sky
    Wheeler, Opal The Miracle Dish
    Wheeler, Opal, old titles
  - Wheeler - Wolff (Box 79)
    Wheeler, Opal Peter Tchaikowsky and the Nutcracker
    Wheeler, Opal Ballet
    White, Hilda Song Without End
    White, Hilda Wild Decembers